[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":167904,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":748788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":8790,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":757581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":18077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":775659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3013,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":778676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":784236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2107,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":786344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the seco nd one t o it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":11520,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":797864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1999,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":799864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4834,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":804699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1881,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":806581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":810928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<su b>6</sub > 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1810,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":812739,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":818041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1611,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":819653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br / > (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":822847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1821,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":824668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your r esult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":829353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1512,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":830868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3101,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":833971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1822,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":835794,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":839364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1592,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":840958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":27905,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":868871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own i nverse u nder +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":59482,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":928354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":934759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2817,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":937576,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br / > (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":943003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1882,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":944885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4132,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":949019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1601,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":950620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":954042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity und er +<sub >6</sub>.","rt":1502,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":955544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":5160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":960705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5687,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":966393,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can sim ply be p erformed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":80395,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1046788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</ sub> 2,  but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":120571,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1167360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":22491,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1189853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":9486,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1199341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br />  (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":28536,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1227878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":6760,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1234639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":22882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1257522,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":11595,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1269118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7729,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1276849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":5168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1282019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question wi th feedb ack to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":21783,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1303803,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5372,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1309175,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1670,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1310845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1315829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5900,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1321730,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1330620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":7000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1337622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4764,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1342386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":13067,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1355454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"add 4 plus 1, which is 5 and leave it alone since it is under 9","explanation_history":["add 4 plus 2","add 4 plus 1 ","add 4 plus 1, which is 5 and leave it alone w","add 4 plus 1, which is 5 and leave it alone since it is under 9"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":48322,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1403777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which equals 3","explanation_history":["add 8 pls","add 8 plys","add 8 ply","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and substr","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subst ","add 8  plus 4, which is 12, and subs","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which is","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which iqua","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which iqu","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which iq","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which i","add 8 plus 4, which is 12, and subtract 9, which equals 3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":30110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1433888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"Because adding 0 to every number gives you a number under 9","explanation_history":["be","b","Because adding 0 to every number gives you a number under 9"],"response_history":["0"],"rt":32974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1466863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":17684,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1484548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":5581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1490130,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":9051,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1499182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, with the number 3 that is going to be 6","explanation_history":["inveser","invese","inves","inverse is what you can add to the u","inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, her","inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, he","inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, h","inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, with the number 3 that is going be","inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, with the number 3 that is going b","inverse is what you can add to the number to give you 9, with the number 3 that is go ing to b e 6"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":38647,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1537830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number to result in a lower number than 9","explanation_history":["Adding 2 to 9","Adding 2 to 7","Adding 2 to 8, gives","Adding 2 to all the numbers gives you","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it","Not sure, but I'd say yes, i","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number to","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number t","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number and","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number an","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number a","Not sure,  but I'd  say yes, it can be added to each number wthout","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number wthou","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number wtho","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number wth","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number wt","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number w","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number with the","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number with th","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number with t","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number with ","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number with","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number wit","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number wi","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number w","Not sure, but I'd say yes, it can be added to each number to result in a lower number","Not sur e, but I 'd say yes, it can be added to each number to result in a lower number than 9"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":192700,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1730532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes, because 3 can be added to all relevant numbers under 9 and produce each number again","explanation_history":["Yes, so 2","Yes, so ","Yes, so","Yes, s","Yes, because 2","Yes, because 3 can be added to all numbers under","Yes, because 3 can be added to all nu","Yes, because 3 can be added to all n","Yes, because 3 can be added to all ","Yes, because 3 can be added to all relevant numbers under 9 to result in the","Yes, because 3 can be added to all relevant numbers under 9 to ","Yes, because 3 can be added to  all rele vant numbers under 9 to","Yes, because 3 can be added to all relevant numbers under 9 t","Yes, because 3 can be added to all relevant numbers under 9 and produce each number again"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":147036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1877570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I think it is, I think it could produce all numbers under 9, but might be missing one or two that it can't.","explanation_history":["5 would leave out a few numbers","5 would l","5 would ","5 would","5 wouldn't produce a "," ","I think it is, I think it could re","I think it is, I think it could r","I think it is, I think it could produce all numbers under 9, but might be missing one or two that it can't."],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":113755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1991328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I think so, I think it produces all the numbers under 9","explanation_history":["I think so, I think it produces all the numbers under 9"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":69737,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2061066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the ar bitrary  value if necessary.","rt":18243,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2079309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1=X","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-9","n-1=X"],"rt":42306,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2121616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x=y","explain":true,"explanation":"Subtract X from N (i.e., N-X) to get the inverse Y","explanation_history":["N","N","If","I","N","Substract X from N to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N  to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from  N ( to  get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i. to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e. to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e., to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e.,  to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e., N to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e., N- to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e., N-X to get the inverse Y","Subtract X from N (i.e., N-X) to get the inverse Y"],"response_history":["n-x=Y","n-x=y"],"rt":73332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2194950,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would h ave to w rite it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers up to N.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm sure there is, but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to go","I'm sure there is, but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to g","I'm sure there is, but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is,  but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, th but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, the but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, ther but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there but I  would h ave to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there  but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there a but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there al but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there alwa but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there alway but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always  but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure ther e is, th ere always is, but I would have to write it out. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out t. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to c. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to co. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come . In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there  is, the re always is, but I would have to write it out to come up . In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up w. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up wit. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with t. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the . In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write i t out to  come up with the fu. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the fun. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the funt. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the func. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the functi. In general, I think the pattern has to do with","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with it","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with i","I'm sure there is, there always is, but  I would  have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there bein","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there bei","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there be","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can results ","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can results","I'm sure there is, the re alway s is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can resultin ","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can resultin","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can resulti","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers that","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers tha","I'm sure there is , there  always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers th","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers t","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers le","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there being a forumla that can result in the sequential numbers l","I'm sure there is, there always is, but I would have to write it out to come up with the function. In general, I think the pattern has to do with  there  being a  forumla that can result in the sequential numbers up to N."],"rt":92224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2287175,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16745,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2303922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2313094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16765,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2329860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 wasn't a generator of 6, and that's not a multiple of 6 either.","explanation_history":["Without thinking about it too  much, I 'd say false, because 4 wasn't a divo","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 isn't a divor","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 isn't a divo","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 isn't a divs","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 isn't a divisor of 6, and","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 isn't a divisor of 6, an","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 is","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 i","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 wasn't a generator of 6, and that's not a mil","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 wasn't a generator of 6, and that's not a mi","Without thinking about it too much, I'd say false, because 4 wasn't a generator of 6, and that's not a multiple of 6 either."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":61656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2391519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always","Sometimes","Always","Sometimes","Never","Always","Sometimes","Always","Sometimes"],"rt":239645,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2631165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why, but mostly because never is incorrect and it's hard to say always for a rule like this to me.","explanation_history":["I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why ","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why. Never is c","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why. Ne","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why. N","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why. ","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why.","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why, but no","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why, but n","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why, but mostly because never is c","I would say sometimes, but can't say for certain why, but mostly because never is incorrect and it's hard to say always for a rule like this to me."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":49061,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2680230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":24858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2705092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2547,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2707640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"36","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["36"],"rt":3513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2711153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Masters Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Masters Degree"],"rt":4131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2715285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College Calculus I'd say. Always took hono rs math  since young age, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calcuis ","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calcuis","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calcui","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calcus","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calcu ","Colle ge Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and aslo","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and asl","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and as","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and aso too","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and aso t o","Coll ege Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and aso t","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and aso ","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and aso","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and as","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and a","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc clas s in a s tep above in college and alt","College Calculus. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college.","College Calculus . Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college.","College Calculus I. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college.","College Calculus I'd. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college.","College Calculus I'd . Always took honors math,  it's be en a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college.","College Calculus I'd sa. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced, but can't be ","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced, bu","C ollege C alculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced, b","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced, ","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced,","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step  above i n college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math , it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math s, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd sa y. Alway s took honors math snc, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math snce, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math snc, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math sn, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in  college  and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math s, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math sin, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math sinc, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd sa y. Alway s took honors math since, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math since , it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math since y, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math since you, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in  a step a bove in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math since young, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math since young a, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc is the most advanced.","College Calculus I'd say. Always took honors math since young age, it's been a while though. I took AB and BC Calculus in High School. Took another Calc class in a step above in college and also took statistics and econometrics classes in college. I'd say the College Calc i s the mo st advanced."],"rt":111897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2827185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":11938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2839125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used  it but  not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":7664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2846789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely","2 - somewhat"],"rt":10546,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2857336,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewh at","3 -  definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4089,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2861426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2865497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2788,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2868285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2872404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, that would have made things SO much easier","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No, that would have made things SO much easier for me","No, that would have made things SO much easier for m","No, that would have made things SO much easier for ","No, that would have made things SO much easier for","No, that would  have ma de things SO much easier fo","No, that would have made things SO much easier f","No, that would have made things SO much easier ","No, that would have made things SO much easier"],"rt":14400,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2886805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, this was great. I miss doing math, it was always my favorite.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes, this was great. I miss doing math regularly","Yes, this was great. I miss doing math re","Yes, this was great. I miss doing math r","Yes, this was great. I miss doing math ","Yes, this was great. I miss doing math, it was always my favorite."],"rt":18150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2904956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]